[Speed and Love]
[السرعة والحب]
[Episode 15]
[الحلقة 15]
You've had too much to drink.
لقد شربت أكثر من اللازم.
No.
لا.
I'm perfectly sober.
أنا بكامل وعيي.
The foundation course is over.
انتهت الدورة التأسيسية.
Tell me,
أخبرني،
which school should I apply to?
أي جامعة يجب أن أتقدم إليها؟
You should discuss it with your mother.
ينبغي عليك مناقشة الأمر مع والدتك.
She doesn't want me to stay here.
إنها لا تريدني أن أبقى هنا.
She wants me to go to Canada
تريدني أن أذهب إلى كندا
to live with her.
أن يعيش معها.
Jin Zhao.
جين تشاو.
If I leave,
إذا غادرت،
I won't be able to come back for a long time.
لن أتمكن من العودة لفترة طويلة.
Will you miss me?
هل ستشتاق إلي؟
♪ Faded light that pulls me far ♪
♪ ضوء خافت يجذبني بعيدًا ♪
♪ Chase the whispers where you are ♪
♪ اتبع الهمسات أينما كنت ♪
♪ Through the echoing that still string ♪
♪ عبر صدى ذلك الوتر الساكن ♪
♪ Every step takes me away ♪
♪ كل خطوة تأخذني بعيداً ♪
♪ Away from the noise, the endless fights ♪
♪ بعيدًا عن الضجيج، والمعارك التي لا تنتهي ♪
You're out of your mind.
أنت مجنون.
♪  Through the quiet of your light ♪
♪ عبر هدوء نورك ♪
♪ I'll break the chains and leave the gray ♪
♪ سأكسر القيود وأترك ​​الرمادي ♪
♪ Take me far, just take me away ♪
♪ خذني بعيدًا، فقط خذني بعيدًا ♪
♪ Wind is howling and calling me ♪
♪ الريح تعوي وتناديني ♪
I'm out of my mind, too.
أنا أيضاً فقدت صوابي.
♪ Through the forest to the sea ♪
♪ عبر الغابة إلى البحر ♪
♪ Shadows dance, the sky's turned grey ♪
♪ ترقص الظلال، وقد تحولت السماء إلى اللون الرمادي ♪
♪ But your voice still leads my ♪
♪ لكن صوتك لا يزال يقودني ♪
♪ Away from the noise, the endless fights ♪
♪ بعيدًا عن الضجيج، والمعارك التي لا تنتهي ♪
♪  Through the quiet of your light ♪
♪ عبر هدوء نورك ♪
♪ I'll break the chains of life's gray ♪
♪ سأكسر قيود الحياة الرمادية ♪
♪ Take me far, just take me away ♪
♪ خذني بعيدًا، فقط خذني بعيدًا ♪
Jiang Mu!
جيانغ مو!
The chicken wings are ready. Where are you?
أجنحة الدجاج جاهزة. أين أنت؟
Brandy, are you done with your call?
براندي، هل انتهيتِ من مكالمتكِ؟
-Master. -Mu!
-سيدي. -مو!
Jiang Mu!
جيانغ مو!
Hurry, they're getting cold!
أسرعوا، فالجو بدأ يبرد!
Master!
يتقن!
Brandy!
براندي!
What's wrong with your eyes?
ما مشكلة عينيك؟
Brandy, what's wrong with you?
براندي، ما بكِ؟
We're having such a nice gathering,
لقد كان تجمعنا رائعاً للغاية،
yet you scolded her? She's even crying.
ومع ذلك وبختها؟ إنها تبكي أيضاً.
What's your problem?
ما مشكلتك؟
Here, Jiang Mu,
هنا، جيانغ مو،
I grilled these chicken wings for you.
لقد شويت أجنحة الدجاج هذه من أجلك.
Ignore him in the future.
تجاهله في المستقبل.
He just likes to pick on you.
إنه يحب فقط أن يضايقك.
Stop changing the subject.
توقف عن تغيير الموضوع.
You still owe me a beer.
ما زلتَ مديناً لي ببيرة.
Impossible! How could I?
مستحيل! كيف لي أن أفعل ذلك؟
You guys be my witnesses. Do I owe?
أنتم شهودي. هل أنا مدين؟
Two beers.
بيرة واحدة.
I absolutely don't owe you any beers, I'm telling you.
أنا لا أدين لك بأي بيرة على الإطلاق، أقول لك ذلك.
There's no way.
لا سبيل لذلك.
I'm telling you...
أقول لك...
Oh, right, Brandy,
أوه، صحيح يا براندي،
we were just thinking,
كنا نفكر للتو،
in a few days when the weather clears up,
في غضون أيام قليلة عندما يتحسن الطقس،
let's go hiking.
هيا بنا نذهب في رحلة مشي.
Let's find one with a cable car.
لنبحث عن مكان به تلفريك.
Master, come with us. What do you say?
يا سيدي، تعال معنا. ما رأيك؟
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Jiang Mu?
جيانغ مو؟
Join us?
انضم إلينا؟
You successfully changed the subject again.
لقد نجحت في تغيير الموضوع مرة أخرى.
Fate. Romance in the air.
القدر. الرومانسية تملأ الأجواء.
Crazy Jin,
جين المجنون،
why are we gathering today?
لماذا نجتمع اليوم؟
Well, Brandy emerged third in the ring...
حسناً، احتلت براندي المركز الثالث في الحلبة...
Top three in drinking.
أفضل ثلاثة في مجال الشرب.
-Let's drink. -What are you talking about?
- هيا نشرب. - ماذا تقول؟
Kid, don't meddle in adult business.
يا بني، لا تتدخل في شؤون الكبار.
-Go on.
- هيا.
No cheating this time!
ممنوع الغش هذه المرة!
Mu,
في،
what's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Are you drunk? Why is your face so red?
هل أنتِ ثملة؟ لماذا وجهكِ أحمر جداً؟
15, 20, 15.
15، 20، 15.
-15, 20, 20. -Have some water.
-15، 20، 20. -اشرب بعض الماء.
-15, 20, 15. -10!
-15، 20، 15. -10!
Do you want it?
هل تريده؟
We're here.
نحن هنا.
You drank today.
لقد شربت اليوم.
Let's talk when you're sober tomorrow.
لنتحدث غداً عندما تكون في كامل وعيك.
Are you leaving?
هل ستغادر؟
It's getting late.
لقد تأخر الوقت.
You should go home and rest.
يجب أن تعود إلى المنزل وتستريح.
Zhao,
تشاو،
don't go.
لا تذهب.
What time is it now? Why are they still not up?
كم الساعة الآن؟ لماذا لم يستيقظوا بعد؟
My head hurts so much.
رأسي يؤلمني بشدة.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
♪ What would I do ♪
♪ ماذا سأفعل ♪
Mu, what happened?
مو، ماذا حدث؟
♪ If I have 45 minutes? ♪
♪ ماذا لو كان لدي 45 دقيقة؟ ♪
I'm okay!
أنا بخير!
♪ Would I write a song? ♪
♪ هل سأكتب أغنية؟ ♪
I'm okay...
أنا بخير...
♪ I don't think so ♪
♪ لا أعتقد ذلك ♪
♪ What would I do ♪
♪ ماذا سأفعل ♪
♪ If I have 70 seconds? ♪
♪ ماذا لو كان لدي 70 ثانية؟ ♪
♪ Would I get a drink or two? ♪
♪ هل سأحصل على مشروب أو اثنين؟ ♪
You drank today.
لقد شربت اليوم.
♪ No, I don't think so ♪
♪ لا، لا أعتقد ذلك ♪
Let's talk when you're sober tomorrow.
لنتحدث غداً عندما تكون في كامل وعيك.
♪ I'd rather get on that bus ♪
♪ أفضل أن أركب تلك الحافلة ♪
Jin Zhao
جين تشاو
♪ Find you where you are ♪
♪ أجدك أينما كنت ♪
must think that
يجب أن أعتقد أن
I did that on impulse because I drank too much.
فعلت ذلك بدافع الاندفاع لأنني شربت كثيراً.
♪ To talk about the cloud ♪
♪ للحديث عن الحوسبة السحابية ♪
♪ That looks just like a kangaroo ♪
♪ هذا يشبه الكنغر تماماً ♪
I was a bit impulsive, yes,
نعم، كنت مندفعاً بعض الشيء.
♪ And the old man on the street ♪
♪ والرجل العجوز في الشارع ♪
but I was conscious of what I was doing.
لكنني كنت مدركًا لما كنت أفعله.
♪ Sat there with his dog ♪
♪ جلس هناك مع كلبه ♪
He told me to contact him when I'm awake.
طلب مني أن أتصل به عندما أكون مستيقظاً.
♪ Asking you if you're willing ♪
♪ أسألك إن كنتَ مستعداً ♪
What should I say?
ماذا عليّ أن أقول؟
♪ To accompany me too ♪
♪ لترافقني أيضاً ♪
♪ Would you like that? ♪
♪ هل ترغب في ذلك؟ ♪
♪ What would I do? ♪
♪ ماذا سأفعل؟ ♪
♪ If I could fly up on the roof ♪
♪ لو أستطيع الطيران إلى السطح ♪
♪ Would I rob a bank? ♪
♪ هل سأسرق بنكاً؟ ♪
♪ Oh, I don't think so ♪
♪ أوه، لا أعتقد ذلك ♪
♪ What would I do? ♪
♪ ماذا سأفعل؟ ♪
♪ If I could turn invisible ♪
♪ لو أستطيع أن أصبح غير مرئي ♪
♪ Would I drive my favorite car? ♪
♪ هل سأقود سيارتي المفضلة؟ ♪
I'm awake.
أنا مستيقظ.
♪ No, I don't think so ♪
♪ لا، لا أعتقد ذلك ♪
I'm still busy.
ما زلت مشغولاً.
Wait for me at the garage.
انتظرني عند المرآب.
♪ I'd go to the restaurant ♪
♪ سأذهب إلى المطعم ♪
Okay.
تمام.
♪ Steal all the fortune cookies ♪
♪ اسرق كل كعكات الحظ ♪
♪ Read them one by one ♪
♪ اقرأها واحدة تلو الأخرى ♪
♪ Till it says ♪
♪ حتى يقول ♪
♪ That I could be with you ♪
♪ أن أكون معك ♪
♪ Sneak into the flower shop ♪
♪ تسلل إلى محل الزهور ♪
It must've been a tiring day.
لا بد أنه كان يوماً متعباً.
Mu!
في!
♪ Watch how they make their bouquets ♪
♪ شاهدوا كيف يصنعون باقاتهم ♪
I brought you some snacks.
أحضرت لك بعض الوجبات الخفيفة.
♪ So I could finally use ♪
♪ حتى أتمكن أخيرًا من استخدامها ♪
-You're welcome. -Thank you, Mu.
- على الرحب والسعة. - شكراً لك يا مو.
Thanks!
شكرًا!
I happen to be hungry.
أنا جائع.
♪ The flowers I planted just for you ♪
♪ الزهور التي زرعتها خصيصاً لكِ ♪
Back to work.
العودة إلى العمل.
♪ Would you like that? ♪
♪ هل ترغب في ذلك؟ ♪
I might take a bit longer.
قد يستغرق الأمر وقتاً أطول قليلاً.
I can't leave yet.
لا أستطيع المغادرة الآن.
♪ Would you like that? ♪
♪ هل ترغب في ذلك؟ ♪
[Speeding Auto House]
[بيت سيارات السرعة]
Take this car out tomorrow.
أخرج هذه السيارة غداً.
Check what the shock absorber damping should be set to.
تحقق من إعدادات التخميد المناسبة لممتص الصدمات .
Okay.
تمام.
Mu.
في.
We're finishing work and leaving first.
سننهي العمل ونغادر أولاً.
Are you waiting for Brandy?
هل تنتظر براندي؟
Alright, we're heading out first, then.
حسنًا، سننطلق أولًا إذن.
-Bye-bye.
مع السلامة.
Sober now?
هل أنت رصين الآن؟
Don't you have anything to say to me?
أليس لديك ما تقوله لي؟
If you think you were being impulsive yesterday
إذا كنت تعتقد أنك كنت مندفعًا بالأمس
and you regret it now,
وتندم على ذلك الآن،
it's not too late.
لم يفت الأوان بعد.
I don't regret it at all.
لا أشعر بالندم على الإطلاق.
It was a bit impulsive—yes—
كان الأمر متسرعاً بعض الشيء - نعم -
and I was too confused to feel anything.
وكنت في حالة من الارتباك الشديد لدرجة أنني لم أشعر بأي شيء.
Come with me.
تعال معي.
All my life,
طوال حياتي،
people have come and gone.
لقد أتى الناس ورحلوا.
I've never been serious about anyone.
لم أكن جاداً أبداً في علاقتي بأي شخص.
So once I get serious,
لذا بمجرد أن أصبح جادًا،
I probably won't give you a chance to change your mind.
ربما لن أمنحك فرصة لتغيير رأيك.
I won't change my mind.
لن أغير رأيي.
♪ Stars are twinkling in the sky ♪
♪ النجوم تتلألأ في السماء ♪
♪ Like your twinkling eyes ♪
♪ مثل عينيكِ المتلألئتين ♪
♪ Telling me ♪
♪ يخبرني ♪
♪ A beautiful dream from afar ♪
♪ حلم جميل من بعيد ♪
♪ Night is painted with neon lights ♪
♪ الليل مُزيّن بأضواء النيون ♪
♪ The softly bustling street ♪
♪ الشارع الهادئ الصاخب ♪
♪ I paused and wandered far ♪
♪ توقفتُ وتجولتُ بعيداً ♪
♪ You're like a breeze ♪
♪ أنتِ كالنسيم ♪
You're giving it to me?
هل ستعطيني إياه؟
♪ I watch you leave ♪
♪ أراك تغادر ♪
Do you know where this came from?
هل تعرف من أين أتى هذا؟
♪ I wish I could hug you from the back ♪
♪ أتمنى لو أستطيع معانقتك من الخلف ♪
♪ Lingering in the air ♪
♪ عالقة في الهواء ♪
My mother left it to me.
تركتها لي والدتي.
♪ Your breath is everywhere ♪
♪ أنفاسك في كل مكان ♪
♪ Waiting, still waiting ♪
♪ أنتظر، ما زلت أنتظر ♪
You mean
تقصد
♪ You, weaving through my heart ♪
♪ أنتِ، تنسجين خيوطكِ في قلبي ♪
your birth mother?
والدتك البيولوجية؟
♪ My thoughts of you will never cease ♪
♪ لن تتوقف أفكاري عنك أبداً ♪
Then...
ثم...
♪ Waiting for your ship to arrive ♪
♪ في انتظار وصول سفينتك ♪
this is the only thing
هذا هو الشيء الوحيد
your parents left you.
لقد تركك والداك.
♪ Waiting, still waiting ♪
♪ أنتظر، ما زلت أنتظر ♪
You are willing to give it to me?
هل أنت مستعد لإعطائها لي؟
♪ You, chasing after the moon ♪
♪ أنتَ، تطارد القمر ♪
I couldn't give it to you before.
لم أستطع أن أعطيك إياه من قبل.
♪ Scattered across the sky ♪
♪ متناثرة في السماء ♪
But now...
لكن الآن...
Why is it okay now?
لماذا أصبح الأمر مقبولاً الآن؟
♪ And me, here by your side ♪
♪ وأنا هنا بجانبك ♪
♪ No matter if it's clear or rainy tonight ♪
♪ سواء كانت السماء صافية أو ممطرة الليلة ♪
I'd have to start with the origin of this thing.
سأبدأ بأصل هذا الشيء.
I'll tell you about it slowly in the future.
سأخبركم بذلك تدريجياً في المستقبل.
♪ I'll light it up, for you ♪
♪ سأضيء المكان من أجلك ♪
♪ Waiting, still waiting ♪
♪ أنتظر، ما زلت أنتظر ♪
♪ You, weaving through my heart ♪
♪ أنتِ، تنسجين خيوطكِ في قلبي ♪
You brought so many snacks.
لقد أحضرت الكثير من الوجبات الخفيفة.
♪ My thoughts of you will never cease ♪
♪ لن تتوقف أفكاري عنك أبداً ♪
It's like you're moving in.
الأمر أشبه بانتقالك للعيش هنا.
♪ Waiting for your ship to arrive ♪
♪ في انتظار وصول سفينتك ♪
♪ I'm still waiting, still waiting ♪
♪ ما زلت أنتظر، ما زلت أنتظر ♪
♪ You, chasing after the moon ♪
♪ أنتَ، تطارد القمر ♪
Well...
حسنًا...
♪ Scattered across the sky ♪
♪ متناثرة في السماء ♪
Can I stay here tonight?
هل يمكنني البقاء هنا الليلة؟
♪ And me, here by your side ♪
♪ وأنا هنا بجانبك ♪
♪ No matter if it's clear or rainy tonight ♪
♪ سواء كانت السماء صافية أو ممطرة الليلة ♪
What do you think?
ماذا تعتقد؟
I think it might not be appropriate.
أعتقد أن ذلك قد لا يكون مناسباً.
Then why ask?
فلماذا السؤال إذن؟
But I want to stay.
لكنني أريد البقاء.
♪ I'll light it up, for you ♪
♪ سأضيء المكان من أجلك ♪
I think I might be being a bit rebellious.
أعتقد أنني ربما أكون متمرداً بعض الشيء.
It's true.
هذا صحيح.
The router at Dad's place is broken.
جهاز التوجيه (الراوتر) في منزل أبي معطل.
I can't surf the web at home. It's boring.
لا أستطيع تصفح الإنترنت في المنزل. إنه ممل.
Just take it as I'm staying here
اعتبرني مقيماً هنا.
for the Wi-Fi. How's that?
لشبكة الواي فاي. كيف يبدو ذلك؟
Are you going to call Mrs. Zhao?
هل ستتصل بالسيدة تشاو؟
Won't she think
ألن تفكر
there's something between us?
هل هناك شيء ما بيننا؟
Then you should go back now.
إذن عليك العودة الآن.
Just tell her...
فقط أخبرها...
Tell her that...
أخبرها بذلك...
I'm only staying here
سأبقى هنا فقط
to use your Wi-Fi.
لاستخدام شبكة الواي فاي الخاصة بك.
Do you think she'll believe that?
هل تعتقد أنها ستصدق ذلك؟
What do you think?
ماذا تعتقد؟
I think
أظن
she'll believe whatever you say.
ستصدق أي شيء تقوله.
Say it exactly as I told you.
قلها بالضبط كما قلت لك.
Did Mrs. Zhao agree?
هل وافقت السيدة تشاو؟
Don't you want to try it?
ألا تريد تجربته؟
Why is it sweet?
لماذا هو حلو؟
Not all coffee is bitter.
ليست كل أنواع القهوة مُرّة.
I won't let you have bitter things.
لن أدعك تعيش في مرارة.
Is your coffee bitter?
هل قهوتك مُرّة؟
Let me taste it.
دعني أتذوقه.
It's too bitter.
إنه مرٌّ للغاية.
How do you want to taste it?
كيف تريد أن تتذوقه؟
Perhaps...
ربما...
(Watch on www.dramacool.club Support Admin)
(شاهد على www.dramacool.club دعم الإدارة)
like this?
مثله؟
It's strange.
إنه أمر غريب.
We used to be apart for so long,
كنا نفترق لفترات طويلة،
but I never felt this strongly.
لكنني لم أشعر بهذا الشعور القوي من قبل.
But now,
لكن الآن،
even though I just saw him,
على الرغم من أنني رأيته للتو،
I can't help thinking about him,
لا يسعني إلا التفكير فيه،
as if we've been apart for ages.
كأننا كنا منفصلين منذ زمن طويل.
Zhao, Zhao.
تشاو، تشاو.
Why are you here so late?
لماذا أنت هنا في هذا الوقت المتأخر؟
Didn't you say you don't know how to redeem your card game points?
ألم تقل إنك لا تعرف كيف تستبدل نقاط لعبة الورق الخاصة بك؟
I came to help.
جئت للمساعدة.
Right.
يمين.
My phone is out of battery.
بطارية هاتفي نفدت.
It's okay. Let it charge for a while.
لا بأس. دعه يشحن لفترة.
Just wait here.
انتظر هنا.
You came specifically to see me?
هل أتيت خصيصاً لرؤيتي؟
What else?
ماذا بعد؟
By the way,
بالمناسبة،
what did that real estate agent want with you?
ماذا كان يريد منك وكيل العقارات هذا ؟
I'm going to sell the garage.
سأبيع المرآب.
Sell?
يبيع؟
You're not going to run the garage anymore?
ألن تدير المرآب بعد الآن؟
I'll run it for now.
سأقوم بتشغيله الآن.
Until when?
إلى متى؟
One month at most.
شهر واحد على الأكثر.
Are you sure you want to talk about this?
هل أنت متأكد من رغبتك في التحدث عن هذا؟
Didn't you say you missed me?
ألم تقل إنك تفتقدني؟
When did I say I missed you?
متى قلتُ إنني أفتقدك؟
Then why did you call my name so many times?
إذن لماذا ناديت باسمي مرات عديدة؟
I did not.
لم أفعل.
Well, I missed you.
حسناً، لقد اشتقت إليك.
Jin Zhao.
جين تشاو.
Where are you?
أين أنت؟
Coming.
آت.
You can exchange these points for 5 kg of rice.
يمكنك استبدال هذه النقاط بـ 5 كيلوغرامات من الأرز.
Impressive, right?
مثير للإعجاب، أليس كذلك؟
It took me several months,
استغرق الأمر مني عدة أشهر،
and they only let me play five times a day.
وهم لا يسمحون لي باللعب إلا خمس مرات في اليوم.
First place gets 200 grains.
يحصل الفائز بالمركز الأول على 200 حبة.
Mu,
في،
the turtle hasn't been fed today.
لم يتم إطعام السلحفاة اليوم.
Could you feed it for me?
هل يمكنك إطعامه لي؟
First place gets 200 grains,
يحصل الفائز بالمركز الأول على 200 حبة،
second place gets 100,
يحصل صاحب المركز الثاني على 100،
and third place gets 50.
ويحصل صاحب المركز الثالث على 50.
Only when you save up 10,000 grains,
فقط عندما تجمع 10000 حبة،
can you exchange them for 5 kg of rice.
هل يمكنك استبدالها بـ 5 كيلوغرامات من الأرز؟
You need rice at home?
هل تحتاج إلى أرز في المنزل؟
This thing sparked my competitiveness.
هذا الأمر أشعل روح المنافسة لدي.
You're quite persistent.
أنت مثابر للغاية.
Let me write down the address.
دعني أدون العنوان.
If they didn't limit me to five games a day,
لو لم يحددوا لي عدد الألعاب التي ألعبها بخمس ألعاب في اليوم،
I could have redeemed
كان بإمكاني استرداد المبلغ
15 kg.
15 كجم.
Or even 20 kg by now.
أو حتى 20 كيلوغراماً الآن.
All done. Just wait for the rice at home.
انتهى كل شيء. انتظروا الأرز في المنزل.
-All done? -I'm leaving.
- هل انتهيت؟ - سأغادر.
I'm leaving.
سأغادر.
Come back for a meal when you have time.
عد لتناول وجبة عندما يتوفر لديك الوقت.
I've come up with some new dishes recently.
لقد ابتكرت بعض الأطباق الجديدة مؤخراً.
You can also try the rice I exchanged.
يمكنك أيضاً تجربة الأرز الذي استبدلته.
Sure, when I finish my work.
بالتأكيد، عندما أنتهي من عملي.
I'm going, Mu.
أنا ذاهب يا مو.
I'll earn another 5 kg.
سأكسب 5 كيلوغرامات أخرى.
Go to the balcony.
اذهب إلى الشرفة.
Zhao!
تشاو!
I want to show you something.
أريد أن أريك شيئاً.
♪ What was it that brought me to you? ♪
♪ ما الذي أوصلني إليك؟ ♪
♪ Perhaps it was fate's design ♪
♪ ربما كان ذلك من تدبير القدر ♪
♪ Through all our winding paths, we always find each other ♪
♪ عبر جميع مساراتنا المتعرجة، نجد بعضنا البعض دائمًا ♪
♪ The storm turned to rain, and everything was swept away ♪
♪ تحولت العاصفة إلى مطر، وجرف كل شيء ♪
♪ Slowly, everything becomes clear ♪
♪ شيئًا فشيئًا، يتضح كل شيء ♪
♪ In your gaze ♪
♪ في نظرتك ♪
♪ I found the answer ♪
♪ لقد وجدتُ الإجابة ♪
♪ There's a feeling so strong ♪
♪ هناك شعور قوي للغاية ♪
♪ Our story is still unfolding ♪
♪ قصتنا لا تزال تتكشف ♪
Zhao.
تشاو.
I want to see this.
أريد أن أرى هذا.
♪ Waiting for the perfect ending ♪
♪ في انتظار النهاية المثالية ♪
You need to come with me.
يجب أن تأتي معي.
♪ It all began the moment I met you ♪
♪ بدأ كل شيء في اللحظة التي التقيت بك فيها ♪
Okay.
تمام.
♪ There's a pull I cannot explain ♪
♪ هناك جاذبية لا أستطيع تفسيرها ♪
I promise you.
أعدك.
I'll definitely go with you.
سأذهب معك بالتأكيد.
♪ My eyes follow you, my heart chases after you ♪
♪ عيناي تتبعانك، وقلبي يلاحقك ♪
♪ I just can't help it ♪
♪ لا أستطيع منع نفسي ♪
♪ When I gaze across the sky ♪
♪ عندما أنظر عبر السماء ♪
♪ Not even miles can keep us apart ♪
♪ حتى الأميال لا تستطيع أن تفرق بيننا ♪
♪ Sweet longing drifts on the wind ♪
♪ شوقٌ عذبٌ ينجرف مع الريح ♪
♪ I can feel you near ♪
♪ أشعر بوجودك بالقرب مني ♪
♪ Feel you're with me ♪
♪ أشعر أنك معي ♪
♪ Forget the sunsets, forget the tides ♪
♪ انسَ غروب الشمس، انسَ المد والجزر ♪
♪ Watch the years pass and wander the world ♪
♪ شاهد مرور السنين وتجول في العالم ♪
♪ You're the only one in my heart ♪
♪ أنتِ الوحيدة في قلبي ♪
♪ It all began the moment I met you ♪
♪ بدأ كل شيء في اللحظة التي التقيت بك فيها ♪
♪ The road ahead ♪
♪ الطريق أمامنا ♪
♪ And every step we take ♪
♪ وكل خطوة نخطوها ♪
♪ Guide us toward happiness ♪
♪ أرشدنا نحو السعادة ♪
People always say
يقول الناس دائماً
♪ It all began the moment I met you ♪
♪ بدأ كل شيء في اللحظة التي التقيت بك فيها ♪
that everything in this world
أن كل شيء في هذا العالم
is predestined by fate.
مقدرٌ بالقدر.
♪ There's a pull I cannot explain ♪
♪ هناك جاذبية لا أستطيع تفسيرها ♪
♪ My eyes follow you ♪
♪ عيناي تتبعانك ♪
When I was 10,
عندما كنت في العاشرة من عمري،
♪ My heart chases after you, I just can't help it ♪
قلبي يلاحقك، لا أستطيع منعه من ذلك.
I lost a beloved brother.
لقد فقدت أخاً عزيزاً.
♪ When I gaze across the sky ♪
♪ عندما أنظر عبر السماء ♪
This year, at 20,
هذا العام، في سن العشرين،
♪ Not even miles can keep us apart ♪
♪ حتى الأميال لا تستطيع أن تفرق بيننا ♪
fate has returned him to me.
لقد أعاده القدر إليّ.
♪ Sweet memories ride upon the wind ♪
♪ ذكريات جميلة تحلق مع الريح ♪
♪ I can feel you near ♪
♪ أشعر بوجودك بالقرب مني ♪
♪ It all began the moment I met you ♪
♪ بدأ كل شيء في اللحظة التي التقيت بك فيها ♪
♪ The road ahead ♪
♪ الطريق أمامنا ♪
♪ And every step we take ♪
♪ وكل خطوة نخطوها ♪
♪ Guide us toward happiness ♪
♪ أرشدنا نحو السعادة ♪
♪ We'll both be there ♪
♪ سنكون هناك كلانا ♪
[Epilogue]
[خاتمة]
Zhao,
تشاو،
I've prepared a New Year's gift for you.
لقد أعددت لك هدية بمناسبة رأس السنة.
You'll see it soon.
سترى ذلك قريباً.
What is it?
ما هذا؟
I don't know if you'll like it.
لا أعرف إن كنت ستحبه أم لا.
Go to sleep.
اذهب إلى النوم.
I like
أحب
anything from you.
أي شيء منك.